Atishay Jain

Delhi



linkedin.com/in/atishayjain19



https://ww.atishayjain.in



mailme.atishayjain@gmail.com



9953456828

Summary

Hi, I'm a Project Management Professional with an Engineering Degree in Information Technology, pursuing PGP in Management from IMT-Ghaziabad.

My vision is to be an honest, empathetic, and impactful project leader and to be recognized globally within my industry. I am committed to growing as a leader and delivering value-added projects.

In my current role at Genpact as a Project Management Office (PMO) Analyst, I help drive Lean Digital Transformation for Global Clients using Robotic Process Automation (RPA).

I am Lean & Six Sigma Yellow Belt Certified.

Core Expertise: MIS Reporting & Project Management

Project Methodologies Known: Lean Six Sigma, Agile & Scrum, PMI-PMBOK®

Experience



😘 PMO Analyst, Lean Digital Transformation

Genpact

Jan 2020 - Present (6 months +)



New Technology & Digital Initiatives, Client Visit Experience

Genpact

Dec 2018 - Dec 2019 (1 year 1 month)

- Lead Digital Projects using new-gen tech tools like AR, VR & Robotics to achieve world-class Client Visit Experience.
- Coordinating with different key stakeholders like vendors, sourcing team & corporate business teams for Client Visit Operations.

Operations & Business Development

Centilytics | Intelligent Cloud Management

Mar 2018 - Nov 2018 (9 months)

- Involved in client presentations to introduce the services & identify and understand the pain points of the prospects to map solutions.
- Coordinating with key stakeholders during the commencement of POCs & closing the deal.

Education



🚇 Institute of Management Technology, Ghaziabad

PGPM, Business Administration and Management, General

🔂 Inderprastha Engineering College

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Information Technology

2014 - 2018

Completed B.Tech in Information Technology from Inderprastha Engineering College, Ghaziabad (affiliated to Uttar Pradesh Technical University, Lucknow)

Hansraj Smarak Sr. Sec. School

2009 - 2014

Mayur Public School

2000 - 2009

Licenses & Certifications







Project Management Foundations (PMI-PMP®) - Certybox CBLMS174

RPA Business Analyst Foundation - UiPath

Six Sigma Yellow Belt - 6SIGMAstudy - The global certification body for six sigma certifications 719545

Skills

Project Management • Robotic Process Automation (RPA) • Leadership • Business Analytics • Business Development • Market Research • Information Technology • Microsoft Excel • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • C++